Guide to the Isaiah M. Minkoff Papers and Photographs WAG.086
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files, 1914-1984
  - League for Industrial Democracy, undated, 1954-1983 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Leokum, Arkady: "The Outsider" (Novel, typescript) (I), 1946 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Leokum, Arkady: "The Outsider" (Novel, typescript) (II), 1946 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Levin, Mark, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Levitas, S. M., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Liberal Party, 1947, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Lie, Haakon, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - London, Meyer, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lurie, Walter A., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - MacIver Report, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Kalkin, Yaakov, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - March on Washington, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Marisha [Bronislawa Feinmesser-Warman], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Meany, George, 1977, 1979, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Meed, Vladka (Book), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Memorial Committee for the Six Million, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture, undated, 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: Summary of Institutional Grants, 1965-1979 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Memorial Services: Programs, etc., undated, 1967-1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Menshevik History Project, 1956, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Mensheviks, undated, 1945-1981 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Mexico, 1930-1966 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Middle East, 1956-1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Mikhoels the Wise (Play), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Minkoff, Eli C., 1964, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Minkoff, Isaiah: Biographical Information, undated, 1942-1983 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Minkoff, Isaiah: Condolences (I), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Minkoff, Isaiah: Condolences (II), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Minkoff, Isaiah: Condolences (III), 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Minkoff, Isaiah: Writings, undated, 1951-1964 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Minkoff, Nochum, 1954-1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Minkoff, Olga and Moses, undated, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Minkoff, Paul, undated, 1958, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Minnesota, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Monde Publishers, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Muravchik, Emanuel, undated, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - National Committee for Rural Schools, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC), undated, 1944, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - NCRAC, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - NCRAC, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NCRAC, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - NCRAC, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NCRAC, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NCRAC, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NCRAC, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NCRAC, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NCRAC, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NCRAC, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NCRAC (I), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NCRAC (II), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NCRAC, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - NCRAC, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NCRAC, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - NCRAC, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - NCRAC, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - NCRAC, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - NCRAC, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - NCRAC, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - NCRAC, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NCRAC, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NCRAC, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NCRAC, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - NCRAC, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NCRAC, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - NCRAC, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NCRAC, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - NCRAC: Atran Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - NCRAC: Humorous Play, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - NCRAC: 20th Universary, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - National Conference of Jewish Communal Service, undated, 1962, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - National Conference on Human Rights, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - National Foundation for Jewish Culture: The Joint Cultural Appeal, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - National Sharecropper Fund, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - National Yiddish Book Center, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - New Left, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - New republic: Symposium on European Jews, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Nicolaevsky, Boris, undated, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Notes on Documents, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Odessa: Fraternal Organizations, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Olympics, 1973, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Parochial Schools, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Parodies: NCRAC Meeting; Eisenhower; etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Partisans of Vilna, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Pat, Jacob, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Patt, Emanuel, undated, 1942, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Pension, undated, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - People's Educational Camp Society, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Petal Papers, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Poland, undated, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Progresso, Il (Anti-Semitism), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Randolph, A. Philip, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Republican Party, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Reparations, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Rescue Lists (JLC) for Anniversary, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Retirements, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Retirement (I), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Retirement (II), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Retirement (III), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Retirement (IV), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Reunion of Old Timers, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Reuther, Walter, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Right-Wing Groups, 1961, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Rockwell, George Lincoln, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Rosenblatt, Sarah, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rustin, Bayard, undated, 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco: Socialist Party, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sapir, Boris, undated, 1961-1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Scherer, Emanuel, undated, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Sherman, B., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Schrager, F., undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Schwartz, Soloman, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Shub, D.: Book Committee, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Shuster, George, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Slesin, Shulamith (from Vilna), undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Gerald L. K., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Socialist Courier, 1945-1973 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Socialist Courier: Finances, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Social Democratic Federation, 1940, 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Social Democrats USA, undated, 1975, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Social Democratic Youth, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Souvarine, Boris, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Soviet Jewry, undated, 1953-1961 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Soviet Union, undated, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Speigler, Red, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Stalin, Josef, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Stevens Boycott, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Strunsky, Sheba, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Port Huron Statement, 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Synagogue Council of America, 1962-1981 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, undated, 1963-1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Temple Israel, NYC, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Temple Sinai, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Tenenbaum, Joseph, undated, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Tercentenary of American Jewry, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Theater and Music, undated, 1944-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1954, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Training Bureau for Jewish Communal Service, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Travel, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Travel Memorabilia, undated, 1965, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Tseretelli, Iracli, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Ukraine, Jews in (N. Grigoryev), 1942 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Union for Democratic Socialism, 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - United Federation of Teachers, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - United Jewish Appeal, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - United Nations: Zionism Resolution, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - United Service for New Americans, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Upper Greenwood Lake: Jewish Center, undated, 1951-1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Vietnam War, undated, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Vilatzer, Johan: Estate, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Vladeck Memorial, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Vorspan, Albert, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Warsaw Ghetto, undated, 1944-1983 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Washington, D. C., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - WBAI, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - WEVD, 1962-1982 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Wester, Leon, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Wester, Thomas, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Will: Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Willen, Paul, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Workers Defense League, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Workmen's Circle, 1955-1983 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Workmen's Circle: Education Department (Plays, Songs, etc.), undated, 1942-1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Workmen's Circle: Festivals, undated, 1969-1981 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - World Conference of Jewish Organizations, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - World Conference of Jewish Organizations, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - World Conference of Jewish Organizations, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - World Jewish Congress, undated, 1949-1975 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Wurzweiler School of Social Work, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Yad Vashem, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Yiddish Culture, undated, 1952-1982 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Yiddish Dictionary Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Yiddish Press, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Yiddish Writers (Soviet), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - YIVO, undated, 1940-1969 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - YIVO, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - YIVO, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - YIVO, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - YIVO, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - YIVO, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - YIVO: Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - YIVO: Autobiographies, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - YIVO Institute for Peace in the Middle East, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Zionism, undated, 1947, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Zukunft, 1949-1983 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Series III: Speeches, 1947-1981
  - Speeches (I), undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Speeches (II), undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Speeches (III), undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Speeches, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Speeches, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Speeches, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Speeches, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Speeches, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Speeches, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Speeches, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Speeches, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Speeches, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Speeches, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Speeches, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Speeches, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Speeches, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Speeches, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Speeches, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Speeches, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Speeches, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Speeches, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Speeches, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Speeches, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Speeches, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Speeches by Others, 1958-1966 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Speeches: Yiddish, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Series IV: Photographs, 1940s-1981
  - Ephemera, circa 1980s (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 1)
  - General, 1940s (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 2, Box Shared Tamiment OS001, Folder 1)
  - General, 1950s (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 3)
  - General, 1960s (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 4)
  - General, 1970s (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 5)
  - General, undated (Box Shared Tamiment OS001, Folder 2, Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 6)
  - Vladek, B. Charney: Funeral (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 7)
  - Workmen's Circle: Festivals, 1971-1981 (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 8)
  - Oversized Photographs, 1941, 1962 (Flat-file-folder 7, Tray 4)